VIMUKTHI

MADUWANTHA

UNDERGRADUATE SOFTWARE ENGINEER

No 16, Koongollawaththa, Hettipola rd, Kuliyapitiya +94778453391

maduwanthavimukthi@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/vimukthi-maduwantha-40a163227/

https://github.com/VimukthiMaduwantha

OBJECTIVE

Soon to be graduate with a BSc (Hons) in information Technology Specializing in Software Engineering. Interested in emerging new technologies and like to face new challenges. Strong creative and analytical skills. Team player with an eye for details.

EDUCATION

BSc (Hons) in Information Technology Specializing in Software Engineering | SLIIT 2021 - 2024 (expected)

3rd year 1st semester undergraduate. Current GPA 2.86

- Computer Networks.
- Object Oriented Concepts.
- Software Engineering.
- Object Oriented Programming.
- Mobile Application Development.
- Software Architecture.

G.C.E Advanced Level - 2019 | Central College Kuliyapitiya

Combined Maths - C | Chemistry - C | Physics - S (Index No: 8216924)

TECHNICAL SKILL

- React is
- Node Js
- C/C++
- HTML
- Java
- Javascript
- · . net core
- MySQL
- MongoDB
- Bootstrap

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Organized
- Time management
- Motivated
- Fast Learner
- Problem solving
- Flexible
- · Creative thinking

WORK EXPERIENCE

Agrithmics (Pvt) Ltd. | Intern (December, 2022 - May, 2023)

Working as a Full Stack Software Engineer.

- Frontend React Js
- Backend . Net Core (C#)
- Database MS SQL

VOLUNTEERING

Project Member | Leo Club of SLIIT 2022 - PRESENT

Worked in Pediatric Cancer Projects

PROJECTS

Educational Institute Mangement Sysytem for the Sahethra Educational Institute.

Created a web application to control all the functions happen in the educational intititute.

Eg: - User Registrations, Payments, Online Examinations. etc.

• Used technologies: React Js, Node Js, Express Js and MongoDB.

Online Food Ordering System

Created a food ordering system to make easier the food ordering process of thedailt life of the people. Through our system users can easily order foods as they wish to get the better experience.

Used technologies: Java, Servlet, JDBS, MySQL, Bootstrap.

Recruitment Company System

Created a recruitment company system called ConnectMe (Pvt) Ltd. Through the system users can find nwe jobs and apply jobs easily. And also company also publish the jobs as they wish.

Used technologies :- HTML, CSS, Javascript, Php, MySQL.

Farmers Operations Application

This application manage all the agriculture based functions (Eg :- Fertilizer management, Crop management, Farmer management). Through this web application users can get the fertilizers and crops easily.

Used technologies: - React Js, Node Js, Express Js and MongoDB

Ayurvedic shopping application

Through this application users can buy the ayurvedic products, rate the ayurvedic products and the sellers. Sellers can publish there products and sell their products. This application is done using the microservice architecture.

• Used technologies :- React Js, Node Js, Express Js, MongoDB, Docker and Kubernates

CERTIFICATIONS

- Assured Diploma in Information Technology (DITEC) Esoft metro campus.
- Diploma in English Wayamba University of Sri Lanka
- Cloud Computing Foundation Course Great Learning Academy

NON - RELATED REFREESE

Mr. Tharindu Wickramanayake

Software Engineer Agrithmics (PVT) Ltd tharindu@agrithmics.lk

Ms. Nilushi Dias

BSc. (IT), BSc (Computational Statistics) MSc (Operational Research) Senior Lecturer SLIIT | Malabe Campus | Sri Lanka nilushi.dias8@gmail.com | nilushi.d@sliit.lk

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that the above written particulars are true to the best of my knowledge.

Date: 27 / 06 / 2023 | S.M.V.M Serasinghe